Please don't block me
You're not just incompetent
Your character and judgment are flawed
Someone as capable as Mr. Lewes
Yet you drove him away
You deserve it that your frogs died
Oh my
We were so blind before
Lewes is the one with real promise
Look at those big bosses
Groveling in front of Lewes
If you ask me
Daniel
Only made money because of Lewes
Otherwise the moment Lewes left
Daniel started losing money
I heard Lewes worked for him for two years
And only got paid a thousand
What an ungrateful wretch
Now karma has struck
Mr. Lewes
I sincerely want to buy your frogs
Name your price
It's not about the money
Your capabilities
Aren't enough to do business with me
Lewes
Calling you boss is giving you face
And you're acting high and mighty
So ignorant
We are Forestwood's
Biggest tier-two buyers
Our capabilities aren't enough
Do you actually think
You can sell to
tier-one partners directly
Don't push your luck
You didn't even ask around
Within a 500-mile radius
Anyone selling forest frogs
Must get our approval
Either you sell these frogs to us today
Or
Humph
You won't sell a single one
I knew your foolish personality
Wasn't suited for business
So what if you raise frogs well
Selling them is what counts
Now look at you
You offended Mr. Quaid and Mr. Logan
These frogs of yours
Will just rot in the greenhouse
Mr. Zeth from Huatai Group
The province's biggest
forest frog buyer
The boss of Harian Group
Why is he here
Mr. Zeth
Why did you come in person
Mr. Lewes
I'm here to buy frogs